thank you
also don't know
[Music]
alone
thank you
Dr Khalifa asked me to stand here this
afternoon
I must admit that this is my
first time I stand in front of the
audience to do the football and
it is a big honor for me that because
the audience is not any audience but the
audience is audiences
for me
my
talk today will concerned about
the happiness
is the biggest issue
facing us as Muslims
since I come to another place
where the majority of people are you
know the Muslim or the so-called Muslim
masses
I can appreciate more that you know
we'll discussed this topic because
you can see for House business here in
the Tucson or in the United States where
Muslims are the minorities
that by Talking Tom
we arouse the anger of many people you
can see that some people come here and
you know we have they make a very
powerful reaction because our
understanding people are alone
and so
the majority
the reaction must be very very violent
again and you know I can imagine too
that
most places where the Muslim Masters are
the majority
they will you know give a very hard time
[Music]
at the least because you understand
again
thank you
incidentally there is Khalifa
about the Quran so I draw most of them
you know from the Quran study in this
particular the Quran should be
the one and only software as a guidance
video
see because we started from the
beginning as
um
to accept the Quran at the only Souls we
can
we sort of take it for granted that you
know
however as I said let's
as the person who comes from the
majority
the place where the majority are so
popular most romances
discussion of this
really takes a great deal of products if
you want to say that
from them
and that's it
for myself I'm still thinking I'm very
lucky to come here to learn the real
truth from the Quran
because
this is the place the first place that I
can get the chance to really study
what the Quran is what
therefore I can see the real truth in
the Quran
to my constipation the Muslim answers
around the world are generally the
government to Quran
they live
they do everything according to what the
scholars say or what you know the older
generation of their parents is and so
they are they're never there most of
them nevertheless open the Quran and
study it and they just follow and they
just leave the discussion of the Quran
to the scholars
but we are commended in the Quran that
we have to uphold the Quran and we have
to
foreign
there is a tendency that the Muslim
masses
tend to mix up the Quran with the the
other sources because they accept the
Quran but they also said that Sunnah and
other sources of tourist products as a
guidance to the religion and
in the end they tend to mix up
everything they say that this is from
Quran and they don't bother to open it
from Quran to check whether
uh
one of the good examples that I can find
is
about the prohibition
Prohibition in the Quran is specifically
stated only four
and
but if you go to at least to my place
they will say that
not only the four provision but you have
also at another position like you cannot
be
something that lives in animals that fit
into environment
amphibious animals they say that I'm
sure that this is
in the end people think that this comes
from the Quran and
I met one guy here that say that also
that this is
but
but I said well you know please show me
the personal life
so I think there is a tendency to
generally to mix up finally the mix-up
to run with other sources
that is why we have to study
and the only Quran episode
one of the most uh popular
reason for the application nice saying
that
in fact we need to understand tuna to
explain
because Quran is not complete and Quran
is not fully details
to explain it
in fact
the person in the Quran
Quran is complete perfect and full
detailed
this is in the first
one of the examples in the first 629
foreign
also in the same Surah
on first round 13 and 1 15.
one protein says
shall I see other than God as a source
of love when he refused to do this book
fully detailed
even those who would simply description
of Harbor any doubt
and what if he says
the work of your love is complete in
trust and Justice improve and Justice
nothing shall observate his word he is
the leader of the Lord
so therefore this this person clearly
shows to us
that
this nullifies the argument of the
approaches of Hades and children
that the Quran is not completely
absolutely failed but like I said
because generally the Muslim masses are
equal to Quran they do not bother to
open the Quran and check the argument
another argument is saying that we need
assistance
okay
I met two days ago I met a guy here in
the University of Arizona
that just say that so I think this is a
also a valid argument
said is true
many Muslims also called Muslims let us
know
use this argument as Africa
you know from the Quran that only Allah
foreign
closest one and two
this is the Surah most gracious amount
of time because the process
but most gracious
and the second sense the word who
teaches the Quran so only
we understand and we know from the
current study that only Allah will teach
us the Quran and understand
leads us to understand the Quran
it also notifies another argument from
the habitations in Africa that says
not fear
in the second part of the group I will
try to convey
some ideas from the Quran about having
something
as we can see from the first part of the
Google we
we clearly see from the Quran that we
don't make traditions
sort of religious duties because we have
the one and only shop which is the
program
and the Quran is fully detailed
complete and you don't need any other
sources to explain the Quran and Only
God
look at that
no wait why
is that why the question is why
existence what is the purpose of that
before we discuss that we'll improve
we will see that
actually as
a source of the religious duties in the
quranis
other sauces
so far
the Quran says that we don't need any
other sources and definitely pass
ionate
but I didn't know itself is also talking
about itself because
if we
treat many or Spanish books about
tradition too now you can see that there
are so many contributions
and so we cannot
we cannot accept that as a source of
religious
do this
if you use
in mathematical diagram we use what we
call
proof by contradiction so we want to do
something
that something was wrong
we assume first that this is correct and
then we find something inside that
contradicts
assumption therefore we can prove that
it is something is wrong
and I think this argument can be used
also to prove that having too much wrong
because
when we read the various book of Hadith
this
we can find that
there are many statements statements in
addition soon as some of them
saying that
the prophet Muhammad says
Muhammad
but the problem says in one of his
according to them
but do not write anything from me except
from the Quran
so anything that you write for me
decided to run he shall erase it
and therefore this also said
that we assume that I didn't know is
wrong we have to accept this
and therefore this statement says that
we cannot read or we cannot try anything
from him except
for Allah to us through Muhammad so
inside a
everything besides the Quran we cannot
follow that the only father Muhammad
when he talks about the Quran so this
Hadith says that because we
we cannot write anything from him except
from the Quran
this nullifies the argument that we have
to follow her business because the
argument is we assume that the
this is
correct but be part of the dictionary
so we prove that this is wrong
another thing is Hadith that says
when somebody asks the wife of prophet
Muhammad Aisha
to explain
about the character of Muhammad
you should follow and how much he says
is
therefore
to follow Muhammad means to follow us
and nothing else
and also
you understand that
Quran says we don't need any other
sources besides
the sauce for beautiful and you see that
it's you are sick also
Foundation First
additionally we are appointed for every
prophet
enemies from among the humans
who informed and narrate to each other
when she works in order to receive
help your love will they would not have
done it you shall be disregard them and
the infections
therefore you can see very clearly from
this
from this uh first that
Allah said from
apart from every Prophet enemies
among the human devils and game devils
dictionaries to each other because
we understand that
then reduce and see the Torah then they
needed other sources
exactly consists of the same thing as
the Muslim world
so when you see that something is wrong
with them
majority of the Muslims do not see why
what's wrong with us because
there's a clearly a fairly there is a
fairly clear parallelism
because the Jews possible
I don't watch it by
creating addition to life
foreign
ly swear by the things you see and the
things you do not see
and foreign messenger
however rarely do you believe
another thing is
a translation from the love of the
universe
we ever made up any utterances and
attributed them to us we would
immediately punish them
and stop the restoration today
therefore the prophet Muhammad is
ordered by God
not to have anything inside the Quran
now after we see all these facts
what is the purpose of that
you understand from this Quran study
that
and this is needed in his Quran in in
this in this world in distinguish
between the true Muslim and the past
Muslim because
the majority of the Muslim answers will
fall into
the second threat
therefore by using the 102 now we can
distinguish between who is the true
Muslim
and who is the
so-called Muslim but actually
foreign
[Music]
thank you
I don't know